So everyone, we have seen a good police momentum in the market.
Similarly, we have seen a very good bullish sentiment in ICC Lombard today. So,
we will
talk about whether this is going to prove to be an opportunity
or it can prove to be a fraud.
We are going to explain it in very simple and straightforward language here.
But
before proceeding with the video, I want to tell you
that this video is only going to be
related to your education and information.
On the small scale, your overall video is for
your education purpose only. Here we are going to
talk from both the technical and not the fundamental view. Here we will talk
first about the fundamental view. First of all,
I will talk about its financial
trend. What is being recorded in the revenue
or we are going to talk about profit and loss.
Here,
we will talk about the performance of 2020, 21, 22 and
23. So,
here first of all
I will talk about the revenue as
I have
described here in the last, in as much detail as possible,
all this is in thousand crores, so there is a
revenue of 11.53, in the year 2020, the
revenue here is very good, it becomes
12.68 and there is a
big drop in the revenue, it becomes 16.84,
in thousand 22 and here again
a great decline is seen, it becomes 18.87,
in 2023, very good revenue is being
seen, friends, here now we will
talk about profit,
we get to see a profit of 1.119, in 2020, here
we again see a rise in profit
and that is more, of 1.47, here the profit
appears big, sorry, a decline is to be seen, there is
no increase here, of 1.27
but there was not a big decline,
but in the year 2023, a very good and great rise is
seen, of 1.73,
overall I like its financial trade very much
Okay, I am moving on with this. Now let's talk about
its financial performance. If
we had invested here,
what returns would we have seen till now?
If I talk about 1 month, then
in one month the return would have been
10.36%. Here in three
months the return would have been
8.09%. In 6 months the return would have been 1.30%. If I
talk about one year, then in 1 year we are seeing gains.
If I
talk to you about the last 3 years, around 19-20, then
I understand the reasons for the loss in gains here.
We had to see the Corona impact here.
You also know that due to the Corona
impact, there were not many insurances in the insurance company.
Along with this,
we also had to face the market crisis.
And if I talk about the returns of the last 5 years, then there is
a great
return of 61.71%. You will notice one more good thing
that from the last two years till
now.  I am noticing that
in the market, now
we are seeing a big increase in returns in this, which means that the
returns which were not received in the last 3 months,
you are seeing more returns than that in 1 month, which
means overall from my
view, I am moving ahead in this direction, this is a
good positive scenario,
now if I talk about the
holding patterns of
mutual funds because we
should know that the big institutional investors who are bigger than us, are
taking a position in it, I will talk about
mutual funds having
14.96% holding in it, mutual funds
other and domestic
institutions having 2.42%
holding and here foreign institutions having
22.85%, foreign institutions are very
big investors and they
buy and sell in huge book quantity of thousands of crores,
so here this 22.85% is
a good big position  Holding is taken here in quantity
and
Retailer Adarsh ​​has taken holding of 11.75%. If
we talk about promoter holdings, then he has taken
holding of 48.02% here.
Before proceeding with the video, I would
like to tell you that change your thinking
that if we pay money in the name of tips, only then
we do
not have profitable information. Friends,
you can definitely join us on our Telegram channel absolutely free of cost.
The best thing is that
we do not have any paid subscription,
you do not have to pay any charge, everything is
absolutely free. All you have to do is, you have given
space to your Telegram promoter,
search for 'Bill Founder' here.
Do put it here. Search for 'Bill Founder'. The
link is available in the description box,
you can join our channel there, you will
definitely visit it absolutely free.
If you
like it, then let's go directly to the
charts. Now
we have come directly to the technical ones. Here
I have put the daily time on the chart. You
can see the ICC GIF. ICC Lombard General
Insurance. Here is a great video.  Pain has been
seen in this, a
great bullish momentum of 8.27% is seen today,
but the candle that goes is a negative
candle close, so now we should
take it in a positive way or in a negative way,
what is it, there is power in creating a fresh position in this, there is
power to create it, or
if a position has been created then should one stay in it
or should one exit,
we will talk about that, but for this I would like to
take you a little by
zooming out here, what I have been able to see
so far, I have seen a resistance,
which I found to be kind of strong,
I had already
drawn it here for you, you can see here,
if you look here, the
price comes to this range from a strong assistant,
after coming from here it goes, then after this
a good thing happens, then it falls in it again, then there is a
fall recovery and then it
falls in this range again, then there is a fall recovery, it
falls in this range again and
then after the fall, there was a good recovery,
a good police momentum, the price went above this
also  I am following the red scenario of price going above this,
but the
negative scenario I am seeing is that the
price has
almost closed below this train line, which means that
now we will have to wait a little bit so that the
price picks up momentum from here and
makes a police scam and sustains above this train line.
After that, we will
see a good opportunity, no doubt there
is a good opportunity here, but it will be a
little risky. Wait a little bit.
If this candle had closed above this train line today, then
believe me, I myself was going to
create my position here by buying a lot of ball in continuation,
but I will stop here for a while now. The
reason behind this is that I will first wait
that the price must close at least one candle above this red line,
if the candle closes above it, that is,
if I tell you the level here, then
if it is above 1200 or 20 or 12
I'll just go with 20
because I'm a little safer.
If I close above 120, then
I'll definitely be
ready to make profits above all this wire.
Here, I haven't rushed it yet, and I've
definitely developed my thinking to wait a little while before making a
trade.
If you
look at the monthly time frame here, the
structure formed here is similar to this one.
One very
good thing that we're seeing is that this
price, which we've been seeing before, is continuously
falling. At the same time,
if you look at this blue line, this is the
five-day moving average line. The
price is now seen sustaining above it,
and it will almost remain so for only two
days.
If this candle closes above the five-day moving average, then
believe me, I see a very
good police scenario developing.
Oval Gas, I have only
told you how many days you have the
contract till the syllabus, if you want to see then Gas,
I have simplified it completely for you,
I do the
analysis for myself, I have given you an update for you also, I
hope you liked the video, if you
liked the video then like the video and
definitely subscribe to the channel, do not
forget to join the Telegram channel, Gas, you get daily
live stations at night, updates related to the daily market, so
please do
subscribe to the channel, definitely
join the live streaming, so let's
meet